Hey, Yermis! He's there! Call a doctor!
He should have healed
from the snails by now!
Emporio! Jolene!
I'm sorry, the wind has stopped.
The rainbow disappeared, too. See, Jolene?
In his final few days, he was happy.
Weather had already been saved.
Weather.
One more time.
I want to speak with you.
Just one more time.
Just once more.
I want to talk to you in the soft breeze.
Weather forecast.
You never gave up.
In your final moments, you were trying
to tell me to pursue the priest.
You even took advantage of Palesnake's
ability to upload your stand,
weather forecast,
onto a disc of its own.
If I were to stick this
disc inside of my head,
would I be able to use your abilities too?
Although the priest has
already started making
his way toward Cape
Canaveral only two more days
until the new moon at
this point I don't know if
I can even take control
of this situation anymore.
I'm so lost what do I do despite the snail
apocalypse we just dealt
with dad's disc was given
to the speed wagon
foundation my old man will
regain consciousness
again and he'll know what
needs to be done should
I wait for him or not
but while I'm waiting
for him the priest might
perpetrate an evil act
again in cape canaveral
oh dad what should I
do please dad tell me?
If I had never gotten inside of that car,
Weather might still be alive right now.
No, I must go to Cape Canaveral.
I have to take care of the priest.
Please, Dad, give me a sign.
Just what is it that I
can do at this point?
What is it?
thread of lies
Itaami o noi Cairo tabi
Kokoro wa eilu
ni togisuma
sareru Cairo kai sareru
Chaka mei no sai hate de
She's...
she's so cute.
Oh, wow.
How is she so cute?
And she's even cuter sleeping
on my shoulder like that.
Jolene.
Oh, that's right.
I'm finally around Jolene again.
I made a promise to myself that
when I got out of prison and
finally caught up to Jolene that
I'd tell her how I feel about her.
I don't have any more time to waste.
If I don't tell her now, I
won't get another chance.
Fact is, my feelings for her are genuine.
After all,
I paid a whole fortune to get my hands
on this ring while I was in prison.
When she wakes from her slumber,
all I ask from her is?
to know and embrace how I truly feel.
Yo, check it!
You see those gators?
The alligators have come
all the way out here!
Damn it.
I think they're so goddamn safe
because they're federally protected?
but they scared the crap
out of us back in prison.
Hold on!
Are you serious?
That one's massive!
Eat this, asshole! Screw you!
Ha! Bullseye! Hell yeah!
Look at him freaking out.
I think you scared it, Jolene.
It ain't running, but it's flipping out.
That ought to teach you lizards not to
mess with us, you stupid, filthy animals.
No way.
She didn't.
Jolene!
What did you just throw?
Let me see.
Show me your hands right now!
Huh? Wait, what?
Yo, chill.
What's your deal, Anastasia?
I'm telling you to open up your hands
and show them to me immediately!
Hey, what the hell?
Seriously, why are you
getting so upset, Anastasia?
Did you really just throw it?
Please don't tell me you did!
You didn't just throw it away!
Urmas, can you do a favor for me?
I want to take a look at
a map to study the area.
Can you hold on to this for a second?
Sure.
Oh, that makes sense.
When you said map, you meant this.
This computer is a total fossil, though.
This is where we are, Cape Canaveral.
At coordinates 28 degrees,
24 minutes north, and 80
degrees, 36 minutes west,
it's the section of Florida
that juts out in the Atlantic.
It's located on a shoal
of 34,000 hectares,
where wildlife and ancient
nature still remain. A shoal?
It's a part of land which is an
accumulation of sediment from a river.
And this place is where
we're currently headed to.
Space Center.
There are no trains or
buses leading to it,
and you can only get
there by driving a car.
With their devotion to space travel,
they focus on launching rockets,
satellites, and space shuttles
into the great unknown.
This structure right here is
the Vehicle Assembly Building,
and that's the Launching
Complex and Observation Gantry.
Being more than five kilometers
apart shows how big this place is.
We'll be heading to the
Visitor Center first.
All visitors who come
here must enter this way
before they can explore
the rest of the complex.
There, the visitors will purchase tickets,
go through security checks, and then
get on a shuttle bus for a tour.
For safety reasons, all other
areas are off-limits to the public.
It's most likely that
the priest made his way
into the center by taking
this route as well,
though I still have no idea
what his true agenda here is.
He's probably going to
lay low somewhere inside
the Space Center until
the time of the new moon.
Okay, stop right there.
For security measures, we're limiting the
number of guests allowed in right now.
Please wait here for a moment.
Apologies, sir.
That gentleman is with me.
One more guest won't hurt, will it?
Come on, get in here.
You would have had to wait another
15 minutes before they let you in.
So tell me, you a pastor,
or could you be a priest?
I try to do one good deed a day.
It's sort of like a personal
goal I've set for myself.
Are you sightseeing?
You know, it's just,
I'm curious why a man of God like you
is interested in all this space stuff.
Because if you ask me, you
look a little out of place.
Well, actually, it kind
of makes sense, right?
God and space are sort
of similar, you know?
And who can say, maybe
God is actually an alien?
Uh, that's just a little joke.
Did I offend?
Are you expecting me to humor these
ridiculous questions with an answer?
Eh?
You did your good deed for
the day, isn't that enough?
If this is your idea of killing
time, go do it somewhere else.
It's not like I was in such a hurry that I
could not have waited
another measly 15 minutes,
you know.
The trickiest part of
launching a spacecraft into
outer space is the unpredictable
problem of gravity.
When launching a rocket,
even the slightest variation in
gravitational pull can make a difference.
That is why when building a launch pad,
it is most effective to construct
it near the Earth's equator.
Because of the centrifugal
force of the Earth's rotation,
the gravitational pull at the
equator is weaker than at the poles.
Perhaps Olympic highdivers
might be able to
achieve a better record if
they're near the equator.
Something's off.
I feel odd.
On top of that, here in Cape Canaveral,
the sea level offshore is quite distinct.
Typically, sea level is marked
zero meters above sea level.
However,
scientific studies in recent years have
shown that sea levels
often vary by location.
Let's take the Maldives of
the Indian Ocean, for example.
Research shows that sea level offshore
is close to 100 meters below sea level.
On the other hand, it's about 30 meters
above sea level near the Sea of Japan.
And offshore here in Cape Canaveral,
it's about 50 meters above sea level.
In other words, gravity isn't
the same everywhere on Earth.
And it can be said that gravity
is weak here in Cape Canaveral.
Also,
depending on the current
phase of the moon,
sea level can rise as high as
100 meters above sea level.
It is for this reason the Cape
Canaveral is one of the most
optimal locations on Earth
to launch rockets into space.
Huh? What was that?
What the?
Where's my drink?
So, Jolene, what are you planning to do?
Are we waiting for the Speedwagon
Foundation and your dad to arrive?
Or would you rather drop that plan and
keep pursuing the priest by ourselves?
Well.
Of course we're still
going after the priest.
Sorry to say this, but we don't even
know if your father is going to make it.
That might be two days from now.
I'm sure the priest's wounds from his fight
with weather haven't healed yet either.
And he's out of allies.
This is our chance.
The only thing we know for sure is
that if we don't finish him now,
it's going to be the end for all of us.
What the hell, Emporia?
Why are you driving so weird?
Stop all that fidgeting.
Don't you know we can't park the car here?
No, it's not like that.
Hey, I'm telling you to move the damn car.
You do realize we stole this ride?
And every last one of us is still wanted!
for breaking out of prison, remember?
Plus, we got a kid in the driver's seat.
No, you've got it all wrong.
Something's going on with the car.
What is it?
Don't know, but it's stalling now.
Hermes, you should drive instead.
Hey!
Yo, what the hell?
What's going on?
No way!
It's gonna hit us!
The fuck?
The cars!
When does this crazy shit
keep happening to us?
What blew up?
Was there an accident or something?
Emporio, get it in gear!
Start the car already!
I... I can't!
It isn't moving at all!
I think the road is collapsing!
You're wrong!
It's not the road!
There's nothing wrong with it!
The guardrail's still standing too!
And there's no wind
blowing it away either!
You might be wondering what the hell
I'm doing right about now, Jolene.
But I...
I think I'm stuck!
Hanging on to this car this
is bad Jolene get out of
the car it's not safe in
there we're all gonna have to
bail we don't hurry up and
make a move we're gonna keep
falling we're not falling
down we're falling backwards
did you say that we're
falling all the other cars
went falling backwards behind
us it's almost like this
road is a cliff the car's
starting to shake all over
the place the front tires are
already lifting off of the
ground now move it like
i said and get out of the
car no this can't be is this
the priest's new ability
it's not even the new moon
yet that's impossible the
force of the pole just keeps
getting stronger and we're
starting to fall sideways
get out you guys hurry and
fail before the car flips over
we're not falling downward
we're falling parallel to
the ground but how far are
we going to fall Jolene here
you grab a hold of Emporio
Diver, drive!
Hermes!
Stone Ocean!
Where did you go, Hermes?
How far are you going to fall?
We're starting to slide!
If we don't do something fast,
we're gonna crash into the rubble!
Jolene, you gotta forget about Hermes!
If she's not dead, she'll catch up to us!
Yeah, but she...
The priest is still somewhere up ahead.
Are you saying we should go back instead
of pursuing him like we promised?
You've done everything you can!
Jolene, your body is going
to crack under the pressure!
This must be it, isn't it?
You're falling sideways?
I just don't get how we can
fall parallel to the ground!
Is it gravity supposed to keep you
planted on the Earth's surface?
This is exactly what the
priest was waiting for!
I knew my old man sealed away some
sort of ability in Egypt 20 years ago,
but this is insane!
This must be the heaven the
priest has been searching for!
There are some plants
that aren't uprooting.
It looks like the Visitor Center
building hasn't fully collapsed yet.
Hey, wait a minute, Jolene.
You just called this heaven, didn't you?
But I don't think that's it.
This is just the beginning.
I've got a bad feeling that this is only
going to get a whole lot worse from here.
Because if the priest has
been waiting for the new moon?
And the moon is what affects
the Earth's gravitational force?
You've still got to make it through
36 more hours of this. Listen, Jolene.
The priest got pretty messed up
during his fight with weather.
I saw it myself.
He's got some serious wounds.
This is our chance to kill the
bastard while we've got him cornered.
If we just keep climbing up this guardrail,
we can make it to the visitor center.
The priest is headed that way, isn't he?
He is. Up north.
You'll do it, Jolene.
Yeah of course i've
already made up my mind.
Yes that's it it's those eyes jolene that
expression when you
look into the distance?
Whenever i see you like this my heart is
set ablaze emporia let's go yeah sure!
I can read your heart clearly.
You're filled with an intense
determination to kill the priest.
And yet, it seems that you still yearn
for your father to come save you.
But what you don't see
is that I can protect
you better than whether
Orr Jotaro ever could.
Sooner or later,
you're going to realize
that you want me to be the
one holding you in my arms
when this is all over.
At the beginning of everything there was
gravity even this round earth of ours was
brought into reality with gravity and with
its gravitational pull
the earth continues to
revolve around the sun the question that
still remains is where on earth am i headed
now what is going to happen next Within my
body and spirit lies the
existence of gravity,
and it shall also exist
at the end of the world!
Somebody!
Hello?
Can someone help us?
What the hell is even going on right now?
What is happening to us?
Is someone there?
Anyone help us?
Anybody?
That doesn't look too serious to me.
We can let it slide.
The phone isn't working.
No signal. Why not?
I have no idea.
I guess it could be that it got
broken in the wreck somehow.
Or maybe it has something to
do with this strange gravity.
I don't know.
Anyways, I wonder what's going
on everywhere else in the world.
I mean, do you think that a
rescue team will possibly show up?
Looks like we made it to
the box offices, Jolene.
And over there is our entrance.
The only way to get
into the visitor center.
Jolene, are you sure the priest
is still in this direction?
He's close, yeah.
I can sense him right here.
It almost feels like he was
just standing in this spot.
This damn guy, could it be?
Is it really him? But why?
Is it Hail Snake?
No, it looks more like the Green Baby.
This is the priest stand?
Is it in a new form?
Hey, what's going on now?
July, no!
Something fucked up is
happening to my right hand!
I've come to eliminate you for good,
since you couldn't wait two more days.
Although you think I cope.
My head is filled with hope.
Of some place other than here.
Although you think I smile.
Inside and all the while.
I'm wondering.
About my destiny.
I'm thinking about.
All the things.
I'd like to do.
In my life,
I'm a dreamer,
a distant dreamer,
dreaming far
from today.
Thank you.